cochinsquare.com 2016-10-22

# Privacy Policy | Cochin Square - Kochi News

We are committed in respecting the privacy of every person who visits our website (the “ **Site** “). In the course of using the Site, we may become privy to your personal information, including information that is of a confidential nature. Your privacy is important to us and we strive to take reasonable care and protection of the information we receive from you.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy (the “ **Policy** “), as amended from time to time, is to give you an understanding on how we intend to collect and use the information you provide to us. The Policy is subject to our changes. Upon updating the Policy, we will also revise the “Updated” date at the bottom of this Policy.

By accessing the Site and providing us such information, you hereby consent to the collection and use of such information for the purposes disclosed in this Policy.

### Personal Information

When you register with the Site, we may ask for information not limited to your age, gender, first and last name, birth date, title, zip code/ pin code, occupation, industry, company or any other physical address, contact number, email or other contact information and other relevant data as desired by us(“ **Personal Information** “). Questions or comments submitted by visitors may also be included as Personal Information.

### Personal Information and its usage

**We may use your Personal Information to:**

  * send you, from time to time, updates or news regarding the Site;
  * respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the http://www.CochinSquare.com/about/terms-of-use/ or as otherwise required by law;
  * transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we may notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy;
  * to send you updates or news regarding the Site, but you may choose not to receive email of this type by accessing the “Account” tab of the Site and updating your notification settings;
  * seek your feedback or to contact you in relation to those services offered on the Site;
  * administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us;
  * anticipate and resolve problems related to the Site; and
  * allow you to subscribe to our newsletters;
  * allow you to enter promotions or sweepstakes.
  * We may also remove all the personally identifiable information and use the rest for historical, statistical or scientific purposes.

### Non-Personal Information and its usage

At this Site we may additionally collect and track non-personal information about your visit including the domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered our Site, how much time you spend on each of our web pages, the Internet Protocol (IP) address associated with your computer, operating system and platform, transaction history, pages viewed, information searched for or requested for, access time and other relevant statistics. We will use this information for the purposes of improving the performance and operations of our Site and attract advertisers and listings for our Site.

### Authorization

You authorize us to exchange, share, part with all information (personal and non-personal), across borders and from your country and jurisdiction to any other countries and jurisdictions across the world, with any agent/third party service provider/banks/financial institutions/credit bureaus/agencies/participation in any telecommunication or electronic clearing network as may be required by law, customary practice, credit reporting, statistical analysis and credit scoring, verification or risk management and shall not hold us liable for use or disclosure of this information.

### Information placed on your computer

We may store some information such as cookies on your computer when you visit the Site. Cookies are small files that are stored on the hard drive of your computer ready for future access when you return to our Site. This information facilitates your use of the Site and ensures that you do not need to re-enter your details every time you visit it. You can erase or choose to block this information from your computer. The cookies do not contain or capture any personal information. You can configure your computer’s browser to alert you when the Site is attempting to send you a cookie and allow you to accept or refuse the cookie. Your decision to refuse cookies will not prevent you from using the Site, but may limit your ability to take advantage of some of our advanced features.

### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of every minor is especially important to us. The Site is not structured to attract minor children under eighteen (18) years. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years.

### Third Party Links

As a matter of convenience to you, the Site may provide links and hyperlinks to third party advertisements as well as provide links and hyperlinks to external Internet sites. The listing of an external site does not imply endorsement of such site by us. We do not make any representations regarding the availability and performance of the Site or any of the external sites which could be provided. If You click on any advertising banner, sponsor link, or other external link from the Site, your browser may automatically direct you to a new browser window that is not hosted or controlled by us and we are not responsible for the content, [terms of use](http://www.trivandrumbuzz.com/about/terms-of-use/ "terms of use"), privacy policies and practices of other websites functionality, or technological safety of these external sites.

### Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you provide us with Your Personal Information, we wish to maintain your Personal Information accurate at all times. If you need to update or correct Your Personal Information for any reason, you may send updates and corrections to us at contact@metrogeometry.com and we may take all reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information within a reasonable period of time.

### Contacting Us

We will address any questions, comments and concerns about our online privacy practice and policy. Please write to us at contact@metrogeometry.com

MetroGeometry

> TC 24/1860, Tenra 31  
>  Near TAJ Residency,  
>  Thycadu P.O Trivandrum,  Kerala, India 695014

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible ways in which you believe the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.
